Skol Vikings.
With the 51st pick in the 2026 NFL
Draft, the Minnesota Vikings select Jake
Golday, linebacker, Cincinnati.
Welcome, brother. Yeah, this is an
off-the-ball tall, rangy linebacker.
Bobby Okereke is who he reminded me of
when he was coming out of college. You
see that [music] speed and you see the
physicality. When you're over 6'4,
almost 240 lb, and you can really run
and carry guys down the slot to go along
with some of that range off the edge,
you'll see him [music] rush at times.
That versatility, you know, I think
about um Vander Esch, going back to the
Cowboys is another one you can compare
him to. CD, so again, we saw these long,
rangy linebackers. Sunny Styles goes off
the board in the top 10. Another version
of that here in the second round.